[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120430pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 25, "question": "NIDENTIFIED MALE: (Inaudible) the order, Governor?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBD", "NNP", ":", ":", "JJ", "NN", "DT", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 26, "answer": "Well, of course.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120430pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 89, "question": "What's wrong with that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 90, "answer": "Nothing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}, "docId": "120430pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "CC", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "POS", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 97, "question": "Do you think it's reprehensible?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 98, "answer": "Well, I do -- I do and going by Obama's own standards, I think it's reprehensible.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120430pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 104, "question": "Do you agree with him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 105, "answer": "Yes, pretty much.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120430pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 107, "question": "Do you agree with him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 108, "answer": "OK.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120430pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 113, "question": "What is the difference?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 114, "answer": "There's a big difference.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120430pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 133, "question": "I'm having a what?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "WP", "."], "aSentId": 134, "answer": "A category error.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120430pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 135, "question": "A category error?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 136, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120430pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "TO", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP$", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "VBD", "RP", ",", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 139, "question": "I'm sure you've heard of that, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 140, "answer": "Explain to me why I've got my apples and oranges mixed up, that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120430pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 182, "question": "For the American people?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 183, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120430pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "JJ", ",", "NN", "VBG", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 192, "question": "What's your point?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 193, "answer": "My point is that he wasn't the day-to-day tactical operative, guy running Al Qaeda.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120430pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 199, "question": "Are we really going to have -- ?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", ":", "."], "aSentId": 200, "answer": "Yes, we are having this argument.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"]}, "docId": "120430pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "RB", "IN", "VBG", "PRP", ":", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CC", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBG", ":", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 209, "question": "Why is it stupid?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 210, "answer": "Because instead of making it -- taking a victory lap and getting the praise that he deserved for the decision, he turned it into this nanny-nanny-nanny thing against Mitt Romney, changing -- stepping on his own presidential message.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"]}, "docId": "120430pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "WP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBZ", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 227, "question": "He wouldn't have reminded his number one challenger that he said he wouldn't have spent the money?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "PRP$", "NN", "CD", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 228, "answer": "Well, first of all, your characterization of what Mitt Romney said, I think, is off.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120430pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", ":"], "qSentId": 238, "question": "(Inaudible)?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 239, "answer": "It didn't cost --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120430pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "WP", "-NONE-", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 241, "question": "Are we really going to do this sort of high school debating tactic crap?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "VBG", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 242, "answer": "I'm curious what you're thinking what (inaudible).", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120430pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "TO", "WP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 245, "question": "That's cheap in the Republican world?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 246, "answer": "That's cheap in comparison to what the cost of the war on terror is.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120430pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "CC", "IN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 253, "question": "Would you dispute that after eight years of Republican administration the country went into a huge economic collapse?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 254, "answer": "No, but that's a timeline question.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120430pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "JJ", "IN", "VBG", ":", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CC", "VBG", "JJ", "IN", "WRB", "JJ", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 260, "question": "I don't know what it cost, the mission, actually, but (inaudible) cheap is part of the problem here?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", ",", "CC", ":", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 261, "answer": "I think the debate tactic of getting -- of sort of standing on a soap box and waxing poetic about how much I think this operation cost is cheap.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120430pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 269, "question": "That's good journalism, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 270, "answer": "Maybe, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120430pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 271, "question": "Isn't that the point of an interview about this kind of issue?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 272, "answer": "Well, you're cross-examining me.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120430pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 279, "question": "I mean, are they really expecting us to believe that if Mitt Romney was president, he wouldn't do stuff like this occasionally?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBG", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 280, "answer": "I would think he would do stuff like that.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120430pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", ":", "DT", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJR", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 299, "question": "I mean, isn't this good for America?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 300, "answer": "I think as -- all in all, it's better to have a cool president than a not cool president.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120430pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", ",", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 302, "question": "Is Mitt Romney a dork?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "NNP", "NNP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 303, "answer": "He's a stiff, to be sure.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120430pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 304, "question": "What's the difference?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 305, "answer": "Oh, the etymological differences are small.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120430pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "RB", "VBZ", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 307, "question": "Is there a difference between a stiff and a dork?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 308, "answer": "I would think there probably is, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120430pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RBR", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 309, "question": "Can you enunciate for me?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 310, "answer": "I would say the latter is more of a geeky nerd sort of type.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120430pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 313, "question": "Could you be a stiff and a dork?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "CC", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 314, "answer": "Oh, absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120430pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ":"], "qSentId": 333, "question": "Do you want to start chanting?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 334, "answer": "No --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120430pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 348, "question": "But just to clarify you are a 100 percent bona fide Arsenal supporter?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "CD", "NN", "NN", "NN", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 349, "answer": "Yeah, man.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERCENT": ["100 percent"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120430pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 371, "question": "Are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 372, "answer": "Well, what I am is actually I'm a co-founder of a voter organization that's non-partisan.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120430pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 378, "question": "What do you think of him as a speaker?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 379, "answer": "Oh, I think he's a great speaker.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120430pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "MD", "VB", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 399, "question": "Are you surprised a politician would do that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "MD", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 400, "answer": "I'm not surprised a politician would do that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120430pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 414, "question": "Would they work?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 415, "answer": "I think so.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120430pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 452, "question": "Why aren't they voting?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 453, "answer": "-- huge.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120430pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 459, "question": "How are you encouraging them?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 460, "answer": "Absolutely I think they have been.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120430pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["."], "qSentId": 499, "question": "What?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "."], "aSentId": 500, "answer": ".", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["May 12th"], "ORGANIZATION": ["National Train Day"]}, "docId": "120430pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBG", "RP", "NNP", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 504, "question": "Why should I be talking about trains?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 505, "answer": "Well, we have National Train Day, which is the fifth one of its kind, coming up May 12th.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120430pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 511, "question": "Is the point basically that with gas prices soaring, gas guzzling cars on the increase, it's time for America to wake up, get real, get on the trains and start conserving that kind of wasted energy?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "NN", "RB", "IN", "IN", "NNS", "NNS", "VBG", ",", "NN", "VBG", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "RP", ",", "NN", "RB", ",", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 512, "answer": "It is definitely one of the greener ways of traveling.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120430pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 523, "question": "Do you still get on the subway, seriously?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 524, "answer": "Of course I do.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jeff"]}, "docId": "120430pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "JJS", "JJ", "NN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "TO", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 547, "question": "How do you answer those two charges?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 548, "answer": "Well, in terms of being the best criminal defense lawyer, I leave that to others like Jeff if they want to comment.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120430pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 555, "question": "You must have quite liked that poll, didn't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 556, "answer": "I like that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120430pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 567, "question": "How much of what you bring to the courtroom is down to that upbringing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 568, "answer": "I think a lot.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120430pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "RB", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", ",", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", ",", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", "NN", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 590, "question": "What process do you go through in your head?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "RP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 591, "answer": "I think it's important for me that whoever the client is, even if they are powerful, important celebrity super star, that they understand that I am in charge until this case is resolved, that this is not business as usual.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120430pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 613, "question": "Is that right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 614, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120430pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 627, "question": "Or is your job to ensure that the opposition, the prosecution can't prove 100 percent your client's guilty?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "MD", "RB", "VB", "CD", "NN", "PRP$", "NN", "POS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 628, "answer": "Every case is different.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERCENT": ["100 percent"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120430pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 674, "question": "What do you make of the Trayvon Martin case?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 675, "answer": "It's a horrible case.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Trayvon Martin"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120430pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 690, "question": "Do you think it should be scrapped after this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 691, "answer": "I think it's a terrible law.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["John Edwards"]}, "docId": "120430pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "RB", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 699, "question": "What do you make of the John Edwards case?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 700, "answer": "It's a sad case in many ways, because I think the perception of John Edwards before this case and before his fall from grace was that he is a pretty good guy and that he might have been actually a very good president.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["John Edwards"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120430pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "JJR", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 711, "question": "How difficult is it now to defend high profile people, particularly politicians, who are by nature polarizing, when you have this kind of overwhelming media onslaught?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", ",", "RB", "VBZ", ",", "WP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "VBG", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 712, "answer": "It's much more difficult than it ever was.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120430pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 757, "question": "What did he say to you at the end?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 758, "answer": "God bless you, thank you.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]